And if we needed more proof that Democrats are colluding with Antifa, politicians are
coaching them on when to throw Molotov cocktails.
They are trying to tell a story, a reality TV story for a reality TV president.
We need to stay away from the ICE facility tonight.
We're almost assuredly they will have right-wing media influencers, agitators, and videographers
to tell a propaganda story about us.
Reality shows aren't scripted.
They're just pointing a camera at reality.
And Democrats can't face the reality that their cities are unsafe because they'd be
responsible for not doing anything about it.
So they're blaming the cameras for the crime.